const popQuestions =[
    {question: "What was the name of Ariana Grande's 2019 breakup album",
        answers:{
            a: "Thank U, Next",
            b: "Sweetener",
            c: "NASA",
            d:"Break Up With Your Girlfriend, I'm Bored"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Thank U, Next"

    },
    {question: "Which Artist Released 'When We Are Asleep, Where Do We Go?'",
        answers:{
            a: "Justin Bieber",
            b: "Dua Lipa",
            c: "Billie Eilish",
            d:"John Legend"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Billie Eilish"
    },
    {question: "What movie featured the song 'Sunflower' by Post Malone ft. Swae Lee>",
        answers:{
            a: "Spider-man: Into THe Spiderverse",
            b: "Drive",
            c: "Us",
            d: "Toy Story 4"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Spider-man: Into THe Spiderverse"
    },
    {question: "Finish the lyric: 'I've been dancing on top of cars and _____' (Sucker: The Jonas Brothers) ",
        answers:{
            a: "fumbling out of bars",
            b: "stumbling out of bars",
            c: "driving electric cars",
            d: "flying rockets to mars"
        },
        correctAnswer: "stumbling out of bars"
    },
    {question: "Which artist was featured alongside Marshmallo in Happier?",
        answers:{
            a: "Justin Bieber",
            b: "John Mayer",
            c: "Ed Sheeren",
            d: "Bastille"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Bastille"
    },
    {question: "Who is the lead singer of Maroon V?",
        answers:{
            a: "Blake Shelton",
            b: "Adam Levine",
            c: "Pete Davidson",
            d: "Sean Kingston"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Adam Levine"
    },
    {question: "What is the name of Taylor Swift's 7th Studio Album?",
        answers:{
            a: "Seven",
            b: "1989",
            c: "Her",
            d: "Me!"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Seven"
    },
    {question: "Who wasconsidered one of 2019's Break Out Pop Artists?",
        answers:{
            a: "Lizzo",
            b: "Billie Eilish",
            c: "Charlie XCX",
            d: "Camilla Cabella"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Lizzo"
    },
] 
const rockquestions = [
    {question: "Who is the highest paid musician to perform at Woodstock?",
    answers:{
        a: "Jimi Hendrix",
        b: "Elvis Pressly",
        c: "Fats Domino",
        d: "Chuck Berry"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Jimi Hendrix"

},
{question: "What band name was also a term used in the 40's for UFOs?",
    answers:{
        a: "The Beatles",
        b: "The Doors",
        c: "Foo Fighters",
        d:"Metallica"
    },
    correctAnswer: "cFoo Fighters"
},
{question: "What musician left his band to join the cult Children of God?",
    answers:{
        a: "Jeremy Spencer",
        b: "Travis Barker",
        c: "Malcolm Young",
        d: "Eric Clapton"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Jeremy Spencer"
},
{question: "Which band name is made up of the first letter of each of its members' names?",
    answers:{
        a: "Metallica",
        b: "ABBA",
        c: "The Arctic Monkeys",
        d: "Led Zeppelin"
    },
    correctAnswer: "ABBA"
},
{question: "Which artist was told to 'stick to driving a truck' at an audition for a local band?",
    answers:{
        a: "Ray Charles",
        b: "Elton John",
        c: "Jimi Hendrix",
        d: "Elivs Pressly"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Elivs Pressly"
},
{question: "Who is the lead singer of U2?",
    answers:{
        a: "Paul McCartney",
        b: "Bono",
        c: "James Brown",
        d: "Carl Perkins"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Bono"
},
{question: "What is the name of AC/DC's 7th Studio Album?",
    answers:{
        a: "Highway to Hell",
        b: "Powerage",
        c: "Back in Black",
        d: "High Voltage"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Highway to Hell"
},
{question: "What was the name of Pink Floyd's debut album?",
    answers:{
        a: "Piper at the Gates of Dawn",
        b: "The Dark Side of the Moon",
        c: "The final cut",
        d: "The wall"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Piper at the Gates of Dawn"
},
]
const countryquestions = [
    {question: "Who is the highest paid country singer?",
    answers:{
        a: "Garth Brooks",
        b: "Kenny Chesney",
        c: "Luke Bryan",
        d: "Dolly Parton"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Garth Brooks"

},
{question: "What was Florida Georgia Line's debut single?",
    answers:{
        a: "Cruise",
        b: "Body like a Back Road",
        c: "Tip it Back",
        d:"Get Your Shine On"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Cruise"
},
{question: "Who was the first black performer at the Grand Ole Opry?",
    answers:{
        a: "DeFord Bailey",
        b: "Tina Turner",
        c: "Charley Porter",
        d: "Ray Charles"
    },
    correctAnswer: "DeFord Bailey"
},
{question: "What is Darius Rucker's most played songs ever?",
    answers:{
        a: "Hootie and the Blowfish",
        b: "Wagon Wheel",
        c: "Ripcord",
        d: "Traveller"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Wagon Wheel"
},
{question: "What city's culture is centered around country music?",
    answers:{
        a: "San Fransisco",
        b: "New York City",
        c: "Kansas City",
        d: "Nashville"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Nashville"
},
{question: "Finish the lyric: 'Yeeeeeeeeeeah' I'm gonna take my horse to the: ",
    answers:{
        a: "Veteranarian",
        b: "Old town Road",
        c: "Bar",
        d: "Town for an old fashioned night out she deserves it."
    },
    correctAnswer: "Old town Road"
},
{question: "Who holds the record for the most performed country song of the year 2008-2010?",
    answers:{
        a: "Keith Urban",
        b: "Taylor Swift",
        c: "Johnny Cash",
        d: "Blake Shelton"
    },
    correctAnswer: "Taylor Swift"
},
{question: "What character did Johnny Cash voice on the Simpson's",
    answers:{
        a: "a coyote",
        b: "Homer",
        c: "Marge",
        d: "Billy"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a coyote"
},
]


const indieQuestions =[
    {question: "Who is the lead singer of the Artic Monkeys",
        answers:{
            a: "Alex Turner",
            b: "Nick O'Malley",
            c: "Andy Nicholson",
            d:"Brendan Urie"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Alex Turner"

    },
    {question: "Which Artist Released 'Texas Sun'",
        answers:{
            a: "The Strokes",
            b: "Lord Huron",
            c: "Leon Bridges",
            d:"Lake Street Drive"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Leon Bridges"
    },
    {question: "What movie featured the song 'Supercut' by Lorde>",
        answers:{
            a: "Someone Great",
            b: "Pets 2",
            c: "Ad Astra",
            d: "The Farewell"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Someone Great"
    },
    {question: "Finish the lyric: 'And when my fear pulls me out to sea, And the stars are hidden by ______' (Sucker: The Jonas Brothers) ",
        answers:{
            a: "my ice and my antifreeze",
            b: "my pride and my enemies",
            c: "my mind and my legacies",
            d: "my life and my necessities"
        },
        correctAnswer: "my pride and my enemies"
    },
    {question: "Which artist released 'Father of the Bride' in 2019?",
        answers:{
            a: "Vampire Weekend",
            b: "Tame Impala",
            c: "Mumford & Sons",
            d: "Bastille"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Vampire Weekend"
    },
    {question: "What was the name of Jade-Bird's album released in 2019?",
        answers:{
            a: "Furious",
            b: "Jade-Bird",
            c: "My Motto",
            d: "Bird-Jade"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Jade-Bird"
    },
    {question: "Which song was released in 2019 by Pheobe Bridgers?",
        answers:{
            a: "Forest Lawn",
            b: "Smoke Signals",
            c: "Stay Down",
            d: "You Missed My Heart"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Forest Lawn"
    },
    {question: "Who was considered one of 2019's Breakout Indie Artists?",
        answers:{
            a: "Eagles",
            b: "Jade-Bird",
            c: "Charlie XCX",
            d: "Tame Impala"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Jade-Bird"
    },
]    
const hipHopQuestions =[
    {question: "What was the name of Kanye West's 2019 gospel album",
        answers:{
            a: "Yeezus",
            b: "The Life of Pablo",
            c: "ye",
            d:"Jesus is King"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Jesus is King"

    },
    {question: "Which Artist Released 'Look Back at it'",
        answers:{
            a: "A Boogie Wit da Hoodie",
            b: "Quavo",
            c: "Offset",
            d:"Cardi B"
        },
        correctAnswer: "A Boogie Wit da Hoodie"
    },
    {question: "What movie featured the song 'Power' by Kanye West>",
        answers:{
            a: "Avatar: The Last Airbender (jk this wasn't an acutual movie)",
            b: "The Bling Ring",
            c: "Fast and Furious 7",
            d: "Straight Outta Compton"
        },
        correctAnswer: "The Bling Ring"
    },
    {question: "Finish the lyric: 'Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee I'm gon' take my horse to the _____' (Old Town Road: Lil Nas X) ",
        answers:{
            a: "old town road",
            b: "farm where I take great care of her",
            c: "vet to see if there are any lingering problems",
            d: "horse race; she's the fastest horse alive!"
        },
        correctAnswer: "old town road"
    },
    {question: "Which artist was featured alongside Post Malone in Psycho?",
        answers:{
            a: "Timbaland",
            b: "Justin Beiber",
            c: "Ed Sheeren",
            d: "Ty Dolla $ign"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Ty Dolla $ign"
    },
    {question: "Who is the most listened to female hip-hop artist of 2019?",
        answers:{
            a: "Lizzo",
            b: "Nicki Minaj",
            c: "Cardi B",
            d: "Riskay"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Cardi B"
    },
    {question: "What is the name of Drake's oldest album?",
        answers:{
            a: "Disarming Violence",
            b: "Nothing Was The Same",
            c: "Views",
            d: "Best I Ever Had"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Disarming Violence"
    },
    {question: "Who is the most listened to Hip-Hop Song of the Week?",
        answers:{
            a: "Good as Hell: Lizzo",
            b: "Circles: Post Malone",
            c: "Heartless: The Weeknd",
            d: "Dance Monkey: Tones and I"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Heartless: The Weeknd"
    },
]    

const rapQuestions =[
    {question: "What was the name of Chance the Rapper's 2019 album",
        answers:{
            a: "The Big Day",
            b: "Coloring Book",
            c: "Acid Rap",
            d: "10 Day"
        },
        correctAnswer: "The Big Day"

    },
    {question: "Which Artist Released 'Talk It Walk It'",
        answers:{
            a: "Quavo",
            b: "Offset",
            c: "Takeoff",
            d: "All of the above"
        },
        correctAnswer: "All of the above"
    },
    {question: "What was Dr. Dre's most streamed song?",
        answers:{
            a: "Still DRE",
            b: "The Next Episode",
            c: "Forget About Dre",
            d: "I need a Doctor"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Still DRE"
    },
    {question: "Finish the lyric: 'Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee I'm gon' take my horse to the _____' (Old Town Road: Lil Nas X) ",
        answers:{
            a: "old town road",
            b: "farm where I take great care of her",
            c: "vet to see if there are any lingering problems",
            d: "horse race; she's the fastest horse alive!"
        },
        correctAnswer: "old town road"
    },
    {question: "What is considered the greatest crossover of artists in Rap History?",
        answers:{
            a: "Lil Nas X: Old Town Road feat. Billy Ray Cyrus",
            b: "Ed Sheeran: Riverside feat. Eminem",
            c: "Forever feat. Drake, Kanye West, Lil Wayne, Eminem",
            d: "Childish Gambino: Childish Gambino"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Forever feat. Drake, Kanye West, Lil Wayne, Eminem"
    },
    {question: "Who is featured in the background of Nice For What: Drake?",
        answers:{
            a: "Missy Elliot",
            b: "Queen Latifah",
            c: "Lizzo",
            d: "Riskay"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Missy Elliot"
    },
    {question: "What is the name of Kendrick Lamar's first Mixtape?",
        answers:{
            a: "Y.H.N.I.C",
            b: "Section 80",
            c: "DAMN",
            d: "To Pimp A Butterfly"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Y.H.N.I.C"
    },
    {question: "Who did Logic feature in his albums?",
        answers:{
            a: "J. Cole",
            b: "Kendrick Lamar",
            c: "Cardi B",
            d: "Neil Degrasse Tyson"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Neil Degrasse Tyson"
    },
] 
